Jaira Arcilla

1120 211TH PL SW LYNNWOOD, WA 98036 | ARCILLA.JAIRA@GMAIL.COM | 425-7918004

PROFILE

6+ years of experience in food service and 5 months experience as a receptionist within the company. Seeking to broaden horizons and an open opportunity to learn and gain experience and knowledge to be successful and accomplish my future goals. I am able to adapt to changes and am a fast learner.

EXPERIENCE

LEAD FOOD SERVER, IDA CULVER HOUSE BROADVIEW; SEATTLE, WA - AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT

Assist the team, cover sections, send people to break, document to go orders, check in with tables, check out people for side work

Post Covid: Continue to assist the team, prepare carts for delivery, organize, inventory, be in line for food production, food preparation, sanitize, clean work stations and dining room, deliver and distribute food and beverages, answer phone calls, print documents needed for delivery

FOOD SERVER, IDA CULVER HOUSE BROADVIEW; SEATTLE, WA - AUGUST 2014 - AUGUST 2020

Take orders, seat tables, consistently check in with tables, clear and set with proper place settings, run food, deliver meals, write tickets, fill in paperwork, work under pressure and in a fast paced environment, provide excellent customer service, multitask, communicate in a professional, respectful manner

RECEPTIONIST, IDA CULVER HOUSE BROADVIEW; SEATTLE, WA - MARCH 2018 - AUGUST 2018

Respond to emergencies, deliver packages, schedule appointments, log reports, print and file documents, knowledge in operating fax machine and copier, data entry, answer phone calls, make phone calls, transfer calls, greet and welcome guests and residents, answer guest and resident questions, work under pressure, multitask

EDUCATION

Mountlake Terrace High School — Graduated High School in 2015

Seattle Central Community College — Prerequisites: September 2015 - March 2016

Edmonds Community College — Business Management: September 2017 - December 2019

University of Washington — Full Stack Web Developer: August 2020 - Present

SKILLS

- Ability to help encourage coworkers and motivate within a high pressure work place
- Work well in group setting or individually
- Demonstrates effectiveness in analyzing customer needs
- Knowledge in MS, Outlook, Excel, Google Docs, Google Drive. 64 WPM. 97% Accuracy.
- Ensuring proper and professional workflow

REFERENCES

Miles Mitrush

Dining Room Coordinator Ida Culver House Broadview Mistrush.mile@eraliving.com 206-361-1989

Ella Cambronero

Manager at QFC Past Food Server at Ida Culver House Broadview 206-380-4585

Ashley Dawson

Mentor Social Worker 425-503-3699